{
  "data":[
      {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Which of the following css property is used to make an element move from a particular direction to another...",
          "answer": "flex-direction",
          "a": "justify-content",
          "b": "align-items",
          "c": "flex-direction",
          "d": "display: flex"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Which of the following css property is used to make an element move horizontally from a particular direction to another...",
          "answer": "justify-content",
          "a": "justify-content",
          "b": "align-items",
          "c": "flex-end",
          "d": "flex-start"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "Which of the following css property is used to make an element move vertically from a particular direction to another...",
          "answer": "align-items",
          "a": "flex-start",
          "b": "space-around",
          "c": "justify-content",
          "d": "align-items"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "What is the full meaning of HTML...",
          "answer": "Hyper-Text Markup Language",
          "a": "Hype-Transfer Marking Language",
          "b": "Hyper-Text Model Language",
          "c": "Hyper-Text Markup Language",
          "d": "Hyper-Text Morkup Language"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "What is the full meaning of CSS...",
          "answer": "Cascading Style Sheet",
          "a": "Cascader Styler Sheets",
          "b": "Cascading Style Sheet",
          "c": "Card Styles Sheets",
          "d": "Computing Styled Sheet"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "The following are examples of Text Editors used for coding...",
          "answer": "Notepad, Visual Studio Code",
          "a": "Ms-Server, Notes",
          "b": "Ms-word, Ms-excel",
          "c": "Notebox++, Vs-Version",
          "d": "Notepad, Visual Studio Code"
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "Which of the following tags are used for creating links",
          "answer": "<a>Tag",
          "a": "<h1>Tag",
          "b": "<head>Tag",
          "c": "<title>Tag",
          "d": "<a>Tag"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "The extension that is used when creating an HTML File is called...",
          "answer": ".html extention",
          "a": ".css extension",
          "b": "cmd extension",
          "c": ".ts extention",
          "d": ".html extention"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "question": "Which of the following term is used when refering to defining the skeleton of a webpage...",
          "answer": "HTML",
          "a": "HTML",
          "b": "CSS",
          "c": "Boxification",
          "d": "Website"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "Identify a self-closing tag",
          "answer": "<br/>",
          "a": "</br>",
          "b": "<br></br>",
          "c": "<br/>",
          "d": "<br>"
        },
        {
          "id": 11,
          "question": "What is the current version of HTML",
          "answer": "HTML5",
          "a": "HXML5",
          "b": "HTML5",
          "c": "XML5",
          "d": "HTML25"
        },
        {
          "id": 12,
          "question": "Browser used in viewing your result when done coding are all except one ",
          "answer": "Google Earth",
          "a": "Google chrome",
          "b": "Firefox",
          "c": "Google Earth",
          "d": "Opera mini"
        },
        {
          "id": 13,
          "question": "What property is used to change the default color of a text to another color",
          "answer": "color",
          "a": "background-color",
          "b": "border-color",
          "c": "text-color",
          "d": "color"
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "question": "What html tag is used to make a text bold",
          "answer": "<b></b>",
          "a": "<b></b>",
          "b": "<bold></bold>",
          "c": "<large></large>",
          "d": "<big></big>"
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "question": "What css property is used to make your text bold",
          "answer": "font-weight",
          "a": "text-size",
          "b": "font-family",
          "c": "font-width",
          "d": "font-weight"
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "question": "These are html tags except one",
          "answer": "<bi></bi>",
          "a": "<i></i>",
          "b": "<h2></h2>",
          "c": "<bi></bi",
          "d": "<h1></h1>"
        },
        {
          "id": 17,
          "question": "Which of the following symbols signifies that a particular tag has a 'Class' ",
          "answer": ".",
          "a": "*",
          "b": "-",
          "c": "!",
          "d": "."
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "question": "Which of the following symbols signifies that a particular tag has an 'ID' ",
          "answer": "#",
          "a": "*",
          "b": "-",
          "c": "$",
          "d": "#"
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "question": "What is the unit of measurement for font size in CSS?",
          "answer": "px",
          "a": "%",
          "b": "vm",
          "c": "px",
          "d": "pz"
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "question": "What is the purpose of the `<img>` tag?",
          "answer": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an image into a web page.",
          "a": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an icon into a web page.",
          "b": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an image into a web page.",
          "c": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an imagination into a web page.",
          "d": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an complier into a web page."
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "question": "What is the purpose of the `DOCTYPE` declaration?",
          "answer": "It is used to declare the type of document that is being created.",
          "a": "It is used to declare the type of document that is being created.",
          "b": "It is used to deleted the type of document that is being created.",
          "c": "It is used to format the type of document that is being created.",
          "d": "It is used to modify the type of document that is being created."
        },
        {
          "id": 22,
          "question": "With what exact Tags can a list be created in HTML?",
          "answer": "<ul>&<ol>",
          "a": "<list>&<ol>",
          "b": "<il>&<ul>",
          "c": "<ul>&<ol>",
          "d": "<il>&<list>"
        },
        {
          "id": 23,
          "question": "What is the closing tag for a paragraph element?",
          "answer": "</p>",
          "a": "<p/>",
          "b": "</pg>",
          "c": "</p>",
          "d": "<pg/>"
        },
        {
          "id": 24,
          "question": "Which CSS property enables the manipulation of spaces around a container?",
          "answer": "margin",
          "a": "margin",
          "b": "padding",
          "c": "flex",
          "d": "position"
        },
        {
          "id": 25,
          "question": "Which CSS property enables the manipulation of spaces inside of a container?",
          "answer": "padding",
          "a": "margin",
          "b": "padding",
          "c": "flex",
          "d": "position"
        }
  ]
}